{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089785525","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089785525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089795555","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089795553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 4cfefb9c-c538-4053-97a6-bd73a5fc8f78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089795790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089795790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 4cfefb9c-c538-4053-97a6-bd73a5fc8f78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089796755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089796755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 4cfefb9c-c538-4053-97a6-bd73a5fc8f78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089798043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089798042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 4cfefb9c-c538-4053-97a6-bd73a5fc8f78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089800977","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089800976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 4cfefb9c-c538-4053-97a6-bd73a5fc8f78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089801832","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089801831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 4cfefb9c-c538-4053-97a6-bd73a5fc8f78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089802152","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089802152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 4cfefb9c-c538-4053-97a6-bd73a5fc8f78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089802859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089802859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 4cfefb9c-c538-4053-97a6-bd73a5fc8f78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089802929","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089802929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 4cfefb9c-c538-4053-97a6-bd73a5fc8f78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ni..ni.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089833311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089833311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" a93cb3a2-38dd-4097-b07c-aa9f79b9ba7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ni..ni.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ni_mno-ni-nda"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ni..ni.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089837884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089837884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" a93cb3a2-38dd-4097-b07c-aa9f79b9ba7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ni..ni.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ni_yo-ni-ko"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ni..ni.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089842235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089842234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" a93cb3a2-38dd-4097-b07c-aa9f79b9ba7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ni..ni.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ni_mwe-ni-bwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ni..ni.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089842463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089842462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" a93cb3a2-38dd-4097-b07c-aa9f79b9ba7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ni..ni.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ni_mwe-ni-bwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089879217","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089879217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" a93cb3a2-38dd-4097-b07c-aa9f79b9ba7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ni..ni.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ni_mwe-ni-bwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089888499","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089888499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" bcd43b0d-7d6d-407a-b431-51aadd6cf39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089892558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089892558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" bcd43b0d-7d6d-407a-b431-51aadd6cf39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089896685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089896685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" bcd43b0d-7d6d-407a-b431-51aadd6cf39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089901149","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089901149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" bcd43b0d-7d6d-407a-b431-51aadd6cf39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089905250","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089905250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" bcd43b0d-7d6d-407a-b431-51aadd6cf39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089910956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089910956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" bcd43b0d-7d6d-407a-b431-51aadd6cf39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089915082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089915082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" bcd43b0d-7d6d-407a-b431-51aadd6cf39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089917706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089917705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" bcd43b0d-7d6d-407a-b431-51aadd6cf39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089927208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089927207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 2f7f6b0d-ad3b-4801-84d4-3606a6d47711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089927431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089927431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 2f7f6b0d-ad3b-4801-84d4-3606a6d47711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089928043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089928042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 2f7f6b0d-ad3b-4801-84d4-3606a6d47711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089928130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089928130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094231"," gameId":" 2f7f6b0d-ad3b-4801-84d4-3606a6d47711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}